// // console.log('test')

//  const question = document.getElementById('question');
//  const choice = document.getElementsByClassName('.choice-text');
// //  console.log('choice-text', choice);
// let currentQuestion = {};
// let correctAnswer = true;
// let scoreTracker = 0;
// let questionTracker = 0;
// let availableQuestions = [];

// let questions = [
//     //sources for questions: https://earth911.com/inspire/eco-quiz/
//     // contd: https://uncw.edu/campuslife/documents/recyclingtriviaquestions.pdf
//     // contd: https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/global-warming/green-lifestyle-quiz/#close
// {
//     question: "What date is recognized as Earth Day in the United States and other parts of the world?",
//     choice1: "April 22",
//     choice2: "January 15",
//     choice3: "June 26",
//     choice4: "November 9",
//     answer: 1
// },

// {
//     question: "Patagonia produces some of its apparel using polyester fabric that includes what upcycled items?",
//     choice1: "Plastic bags",
//     choice2: "Fishing nets",
//     choice3: "Plastic bottles",
//     choice4: "Foam cups",
//     answer: 3
// },
// {
//     question: "How many trees does recycling a ton of paper save?",
//     choice1: "6",
//     choice2: "17",
//     choice3: "100",
//     choice4: "75",
//     answer: 2

//  },
//  {
//      question: "The US Department of Energy (DOE) recommends turning off your monitor and placing the computer on sleep mode if you are not going to use it for more than ___",
//      choice1: "2 hours",
//      choice2: "6 hours",
//      choice3: "45 minutes",
//      choice4: "20 minutes",
//      answer: 4
//  },

//  {
//     question: "Recycling plastic saves ____ times as much energy as burning it in an incinerator.",
//     choice1: "2 times",
//     choice2: "0.5 times",
//     choice3: "3 times",
//     chocie4: "None, it takes more energy to recycle",
//     answer: 1
//  },

//  {
//      question: "How much energy does recycling just one aluminium can save?",
//      choice1: "Enough to power a microwave for 30 minutes",
//      choice2: "Enough to power the average American home for 4 days",
//      choice3: "Enough to power a computer for 15 minutes",
//      choice4: "Enough to power a TV for 3 hours",
//      answer: 4
//  },

//  {
//      question: "What type of supermarket bag is more ecofriendly, paper or plastic?",
//      choice1: "Either is fine",
//      choice2: "Paper",
//      choice3:"Plastic",
//      choice4: "None of the above",
//      answer: 4
// },

// {
//     question: "Approximately how much global electricity output is produced from renewable sources?",
//     choice1: "1 percent",
//     choice2: "10 percent",
//     choice3: "5 percent",
//     choice4: " 20 percent",
//     answer: 2

// },

// {
//     question: "Dropping the thermostat from 70 to 68 degrees saves you about how much on your heating costs?",
//     choice1: "10 percent",
//     choice2: "20 percent",
//     choice3: "1 percent",
//     chocie4: "5 percent",
//     answer: 4
// },

// {
//     question: "Which of the following is an alternative material for making paper?",
//     choice1: "Panda excrement",
//     choice2: "Hemp",
//     choice3: "Sheepskin",
//     choice4: "All of the above",
//     answer: 4
// }
// ]



// beginGame = () => {
//     questionTracker = 0;
//     scoreTracker = 0;
//     availableQuestions = [...questions];
//     // console.log(availableQuestions)
//     nextQuestion(); 
// };


// nextQuestion = () => {
//     currentQuestion = availableQuestions
// }















